In a time and a world of impossible love, he would
accept nothing less than everything.
Every Time We Say Goodbye is a war, drama, romance
film directed by Moshé Mizrahi.
A Protestant World War II pilot and a Jewish girl fall in love in Jerusalem,
even though their diverse backgrounds threaten to pull them apart.
David, played by Tom Hanks.
Sarah, played by Cristina Marsillach.
Peter, played by Benedict Taylor.
Victoria, played by Anat Atzmon.
Lea, played by Gila Almagor.
Nessim, played by Moni Moshonov.
Every Time We Say Goodbye is a 1986 American drama film
starring Tom Hanks and Cristina Marsillach.
Hanks plays a gentile American in the Royal Air Force, stationed in mandatory
Jerusalem, who falls in love with a girl from a Sephardic Jewish family.
The film has the unusual distinction of being partly in the Ladino language.
With young lovers of very different backgrounds with religious and cultural
differences, the film is an account of a forbidden love.
The film explores themes of jerusalem, friends, injury.
The tone is emotional.